quickyellow.com 2013-03-23

# Privacy Policy | We Know Business | QuickYellow.com

IDC Networks, Inc, the developers of QuickYellow.com and QuickYellow tools, understand and respect your concerns for privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have. By using our websites you are acknowledging and accepting this Privacy Policy.

### Collection of information

Information is collected primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. 

IDC Networks, Inc [IDC] mostly collects anonymous information through QuickYellow and other websites it operates. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth - they are 'anonymous' to us. If you you are asked to provide your name, email address and other information and you provide your personal information, you are not anonymous to IDC.

### Use of anonymous information

IDC automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of our platform like the numbers and frequency of visitors to IDC sites and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in an aggregate way. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve our services. IDC may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.

### Use of personal information

IDC will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. IDC will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.

### Cookies/Third Parties

From time to time, IDC or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can not read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system.

IDC uses cookies to store your preferences, and some of our advertisers use them to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

### No sale of personal information

Under no circumstances will IDC sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.

### Links

IDC properties may contain links to third-party websites. IDC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

### Complaints about privacy

If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on QuickYellow or any of our websites, please notify us at [privacy@idcnetworks.com](mailto:privacy@idcnetworks.com).
